teachersfcu.org 2004-09-19

# NOTICE OF YOUR FINANCIAL PRIVACY RIGHTS

                                                  NOTICE OF YOUR
                                           FINANCIAL PRIVACY RIGHTS
We, our, and us, when used in this notice, mean Teachers Federal Credit Union.
This is our privacy notice for our members. When we use the words “you” and “your” we mean the following types of
members:
     •    All of our consumer members who have a continuing relationship with us, such as:
     •    Deposit accounts
     •    Loan accounts
     •    Transaction accounts
We will tell you the sources for nonpublic personal information we collect on our members. We will tell you what
measures we take to secure that information.
We first define some terms.
          Nonpublic personal information means information about you that we collect in connection with providing a
          financial product or service to you. Nonpublic personal information does not include information that is
          available from public sources, such as telephone directories or government records.
          An affiliate is a company we own or control.
          A nonaffiliated third party is a company that is not an affiliate of ours.
                                         THE INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT
We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources:
     •    Information we receive from you on applications or other forms
     •    Information about your transactions with us
     •    Information about your transactions with nonaffiliated third parties
     •    Information from a consumer reporting agency
                                       THE CONFIDENTIALITY, SECURITY,
                                     AND INTEGRITY OF YOUR NONPUBLIC
                                            PERSONAL INFORMATION
We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information
to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with
federal regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information.
                                     NONPUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION
                                     AND NONAFFILIATED THIRD PARTIES
We will not disclose your nonpublic personal information to nonaffiliated third parties, except as permitted by law.
                                     NONPUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION
                                             AND FORMER MEMBERS
We do not disclose nonpublic personal information about former members, except as permitted by law.
                                              AUTHORIZED SHARING
                                         OUTSIDE MARKETING SERVICES
We may disclose the following information to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf:
     •    Nonpublic personal information we receive from you on applications or other forms, such as
     •    Name
     •    Address
Federal law allows us to disclose the information listed above with companies that perform marketing services on our
behalf. You do not have a right to opt out of the disclosure of this information. We may also disclose nonpublic
personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties as permitted by law.
Types of Businesses

Here are the types of businesses with whom we may disclose nonpublic personal information for outside marketing
purposes:
      •   Service providers that perform marketing services for us, such as
      •   Mail houses
AUTHORIZED SHARING – JOINT MARKETING
We may disclose the following information to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing
agreements:
      •   Nonpublic personal information we receive from you on applications or other forms, such as
      •   Name
      •   Address
Federal law allows us to disclose the information listed above with other financial institutions with whom we have joint
marketing agreements. You do not have a right to opt out of the disclosure of this information. We may also disclose
nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties as permitted by law.
Types of Businesses. Here are the types of businesses with whom we may disclose nonpublic information under this
section
      •   Financial service providers, such as
      •   Insurance providers
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
In response to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), Teachers Federal Credit Union does not
knowingly collect, maintain or use personal information form our website about children under 13 years of age, and
this website is not designed to attract children. If a child under 13 sends personal information online, we will only use
that information to respond directly to the child, notify parents, or seek parental consent.
